[ominous music playing]
[tense sting plays]
[high-pitched ringing]
[groaning]
- [high-pitched ringing continues]
- [groans]
[grunts]
[ominous music continues]
[distant voice] David!
David!
- [car alarms blaring]
- [indistinct shouting]
[man] What the fuck?!
- [ringing in ears]
- [tense sting plays]
I need a doctor!
- Hey! Get me a doctor!
- [officer] Yeah!
Put him on his back. Nice and easy.
Max!
Max! Max!
I'm here!
- I'm right here. okay?
- [groans]
- Are you hurt?
[groans]
- Are you okay?
- Yeah. I'm good.
- Hey.
- [grunts]
- Are you sure you're okay?
- I'm fine. I told you.
[man] David?
- [groans]
- Call an ambulance.
Come on. Christophe. Come on!
- [groaning]
- [car alarm blaring continuously]
[fire truck sirens approaching]
[Max] You okay?
[Cédric] Keep going. Don't stop.
[sniffles]
[fire truck sirens approaching]
[ominous music continues]
ELITE FORCE
[alert beeping]
[indistinct radio chatter]
[male reporter] The brazen attack occurred
on the grounds of GIGN headquarters.
deep in their home territory.
Since so many members of the force
live just a few short blocks
from the site
of this devastating explosion.
the authorities have yet
to make a statement.
But according to our sources.
a GIGN member was seriously injured
in last night's bomb attack.
[helicopter flying overhead]
[exhales]
[muffled explosion]
David.
[indistinct chatter]
We turned the place upside down.
That was the only bomb.
The explosive was CL-20.
The stuff from yesterday's operation.
it's part of the half-ton
that went missing.
Remotely triggered?
No. I'd say it was on a timer.
Opening the door activated it.
Low-tech. but effective.
So that makes Christophe the target.
Yeah.
[woman] It's procedure.
You have no choice. General.
They came at us where we live.
Right at the front door.
General's here?
Inspection.
- That's Commander Saint-Juste.
- Saint-Juste.
[Tanya]
From the General Inspection office.
Is that the same Saint-Juste
who kicked the General out of Airborne?
- [Tanya] That's her.
- Why the fuck is she here?
She's gunning for us.
The way she sees it.
we think we're above the law.
In GIGN's history.
this has never happened before.
I'll be damned if RAID takes control.
[Saint-Juste] Take it easy General.
We all want to know what happened here.
Including me.
She's nothing but trouble. if you ask me.
Watch your back.
General.
[David] So. Chloé?
Yeah.
What?
I don't know.
Maybe a clue. a lead. a suspect? Whatever?
Right. We've got someone.
This guy.
The terrorist in the fridge truck.
The one with the cap.
- We ID'd him from his tattoo.
- [David] That on the right?
[Chloé] Yeah.
Turns out he's ex-military too.
We're trying to track him down.
[indistinct chatter]
Can't believe they attacked us here.
At the base.
On the night of the ceremony.
Right before the explosion.
what do you think
Christophe was talking about?
I've always been told
my dad died because a mission went wrong.
You think that's the whole story?
Beats me.
There's the incident report.
You're a member of the squad now.
Go look at the records.
Hey.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
I want you and Nolan
to go stay with your parents. okay?
This is our home.
- Sibylle. come on. Just for now. okay?
- There's no way I'm leaving.
I'm staying here.
Hey. Nolan. time to go. Come on!
Okay. kiddo. You're going home. That's it!
- Aren't you coming with us. Dad?
- Huh? No. no. Go ahead with Mommy.
Daddy's got some work to do.
Take your scooter.
Don't leave the house. okay?
You think we'll be on the team
that's going after those bastards?
This guy barely knows how to walk
and he wants to run. huh?
Oh boy. Fresh meat.
You just got your diplomas.
You're a part of our religion now.
Congratulations.
It's pretty simple. right?
Watch what I do. Follow my lead.
You might be as good as me some day.
That's about it.
I think you get the picture.
So. in this new religion of yours.
is humility one of the ten commandments?
Wait. I'm confused. Since when do
the dweebs from recon hang out with us?
Over here it's tactical.
[Chloé] Yeah. So here. three of our guys
have a visual on the target.
We've got two of the exits covered.
There's one more exit we need to check.
Okay. guys.
Our good friends in Recon located
one of the crew from the CL-20 robbery.
Same explosive used in the attack.
The guy's tattoo was in the database.
The dude has a rap sheet
as long as a Russian novel.
This guy used to be a soldier
but he crossed over.
We're gonna use him to work our way
back to the brains behind depot heists.
And that'll get us
the asshole who attacked Christophe.
The general has given the green light.
but we'll proceed with caution.
Our target is armed.
What we've seen so far.
he won't hesitate to engage.
The commander of the operation is David
with section 3 as reinforcement
headed up by Arnaud.
Along with section 3.
Recon will be on the mission with us.
I know what they did to Christophe
is on your mind.
It's on my mind.
[ominous music playing]
Put aside the emotions.
Okay?
We're gonna do this by the book.
This operation isn't about revenge.
We keep it professional.
We grab our man. we get out.
Plus. we're in an urban area.
So be extra careful.
When we're there.
we'll be on the same channel as Recon.
They'll be feeding us live intel.
so keep your ear to the radio.
I'll lead the convoy
and we'll follow normal procedure.
Form the convoy at the gate.
Last one to join calls it.
That's the signal to move out.
Has everyone got it?
Okay.
Today there are five new faces among us.
Congrats. guys.
You're part of the group now.
You're still a bit wet behind the ears.
and because this is your first mission.
each of you will stay
close to your mentor. please.
- Is that clear?
- [officers] Yes.
Okay. mount up.
Okay. let's move.
Come on! Let's go!
- Go!
- [man] Moving out!
Go!
[suspenseful music playing]
No. you're staying put.
What?
Max. you were in the explosion.
It could put the operation at risk.
Go see the doctor. We'll talk later.
Rapha was in the explosion
but she's going with recon.
Rapha wasn't flat on her back
and semi-conscious in the dirt.
I don't give a shit
how Chloé runs her team.
Get that checkup.
[engines rumbling]
[suspenseful music continues]
[man over radio]
All units. approaching the chopper site.
[music fades]
- [torrential rain]
- [thunderclap]
[rain pelting]
[indistinct radio chatter]
[suspenseful music continues]
[sniper] No visual.
[Chloé] Our intel says
the target is still in the building.
[Valère] We've been in position
for three hours already.
[Max] A man just opened a window
in the apartment.
- [Chloé] Is it the target?
- Who spoke just now?
Was that Max?
[Chloé] Can you confirm it's the target?
[sniper] Got a visual
on the guy in the window.
No confirmation on the identity.
I repeat. was that Max who spoke just now?
Affirmative. that's Max.
[sighs]
[sniper] Negative.
Not the target.
I repeat. negative.
[suspenseful music continues]
Suspicious individual.
Black rain gear. dark cap.
Heading to the depot.
I'm on him.
No. no. no. no. no. Max. no!
No. wait!
- [screaming]
- Deploy. deploy!
[Operator] Go. go. go!
- [music continues]
- Move. move. let's get out there.
[screaming]
- [Max] You okay. Rapha?
- Yeah. I'm good.
Max! Wait!
[Max] Police! Stop!
Police!
[suspenseful music continues]
[women yelling indistinctly]
- [loud thud]
- [grunts]
- [gunfire]
- [panicked screaming]
[struggling]
[screams in pain]
[grunts]
- [grunts]
- Backup. backup!
[grunts]
[Max groans]
[groans]
[grunts]
[David] Max!
Max. do you copy?
[indistinct radio chatter]
[operator] Go.
[officers] Police!
- Police!
Police!
- [officer 1] Clear!
- [officer 2] Clear.
[officer 3] Clear here!
[David] A Glock
and a bladed weapon on the ground.
[operator] Code 652. Come back.
[Djibril] We've recovered Max's firearm.
[David] Form up behind me.
[suspenseful music continues]
[officer] Shields! Coming in!
Okay. boy. seek!
[indistinct radio chatter]
[Cédric] Clear.
[shell casings clattering]
[metal pin clicking]
[indistinct shouting]
[officer 1] Get down. get down. get down!
Get down!
- Now!
- [officer 2] Don't fucking move!
- [officer 1] Get down!
- [officer 2] Stay still! Still. dammit!
[officer 3] Hold him there.
Let's go. All right.
- [officer 2] Zip tie.
- [man groans]
[officer 1] That's it. We're done.
Stop resisting. Stop!
[rain pattering]
- You okay?
- Yeah. I'm okay.
Are you hurt?
Why didn't you answer me on the radio?
I was too close to the suspect. David.
In what world do you go after a guy
when you're unarmed?
In what world?!
Did you forget all your training?
Are you out of your mind?
Did we arrest the guy or what?
The next time I tell you to stay
at the base. you stay at the base.
[police sirens wailing in distance]
What's wrong?
Look.
If you're ever thinking of bringing a guy
from my section. tell me first. okay?
I ordered him to stay at the station
and get a medical.
- A medical?
- Yeah. a medical.
We always take the new guys out on ops
and we never ask permission.
Don't tell me you've never done it.
Max has zero experience in the field.
It doesn't make sense to put him
in a risky operation his first time out.
But you put the other newbies
on the assault squad.
It's too much for him to do
plain clothes surveillance?
You know. run your section how you want
and let me handle mine. okay?
Hold on! If it wasn't for Max.
we wouldn't have made the arrest.
- Whatever!
- What the hell's wrong with you. man?
Yeah. send me that.
That one too.
- We'll need to check all of this.
- And that one.
- [Cédric] Major Bonenfant.
- Commander Saint-Juste. Inspection.
[speaking indistinctly]
- Hello.
- [man] Pleased to meet you.
[police siren wailing in distance]
[exhales]
Who's your boss?
Oh. big man. huh?
Thirty against one.
Dressed up like little boy scouts.
Yeah. Give me a name.
And that other guy. your little pal there.
before you jumped out.
all 30 of you. from your clown cars.
That guy?
I'll smoke him.
Oh yeah? You'll smoke him?
[ominous music playing]
Have a good look.
[breathes heavily]
The only reason you're alive is because
the unit has a strong sense of discipline.
You know what I'm talking about.
You served your country.
But I've got some bad news for you.
I have a hard time following the rules.
And if you don't play ball…
I promise you it'll be a real pleasure
to show you what I meant by that.
[tense music playing]
I'm wondering
how much pain you can tolerate.
[grunts]
You gonna talk now or what?
- [grunts]
- [Cédric] What're you doing? Let him go!
Close your eyes! Close your eyes!
Cover them!
- Out!
- [suspect] Get off me! Get off me!
[struggling]
- [Cédric] Shut the fuck up.
- [suspect grunts and yells]
[panting]
[groans]
[David] Are you down there?
- So is he awake?
- Yeah.
Okay. I'll see you at the hospital.
I gotta go.
Commander Saint-Juste.
General Inspection.
I'm aware of who you are
and what kind of work you do.
You think I'm just a pain in the ass
but I'm here to protect you from yourself.
[scoffs]
Okay. How helpful.
Your job here is tactical only.
Not investigating.
And definitely not intimidating suspects.
If this case falls apart due to
your display of excess testosterone…
you'll have to find
a new career. Commander.
[officer] Yeah. Try to get another angle.
[sighs]
[PJ] Ah. here he is.
- What's up. handsome?
- [Max chuckles]
- You good. Rapha?
- Yeah.
Looks like you missed
your calling in Intel.
[Rapha chuckles]
I'm sure I didn't score
points with David. you know?
In the end. you're the guy who went
after the terrorist. so take the win.
How'd you end up with Intel?
I go where I'm needed. dude.
Not my style to sit on the bench
when the game's on.
This guy's ego's growing by the minute.
[laughs]
Lucky I didn't wait for you guys.
He's been full of himself from the start.
He was born that way.
- The little prick.
- [Rapha and PJ laugh]
Excuse me. where do I find
the intensive care unit?
- Down the end on your left.
- Thanks.
[officer] Can I help you. sir?
Okay.
[speaking indistinctly]
[David sighs]
So. how's he doing?
[Jess sighs] They put him
in an induced coma.
They say everything depends
on the next 24 hours.
And you?
Truth is. not great. Not great.
[poignant music playing]
I called Manon this morning.
I told her it might be good for us
to spend more time together.
So we're seeing each other
tomorrow for lunch.
And. uh…
I was thinking. if you're free.
you'd come with us.
so we can be together. The three of us.
[sighs] Mm. Come on. David.
We can't keep acting
like everything's normal between us.
I'm moving to Singapore.
We have to tell her at some point.
At some point. yeah.
There's no rush.
Yes. but she'll need time
to think about what she wants.
Who says there's
anything for her to think about?
This is where Manon's life is.
She's not moving around the world
just cause you're taking a job there!
We could ask for her opinion.
Is it urgent?
Does it have to be right now?
[poignant music continues]
No.
- I'm sorry.
- [David sighs]
No. it's my fault. I'm sorry.
I'm really on edge these days.
It feels so good to be with you.
[sighs]
Are you going in to see him?
I have to.
[monitor beeping]
[Christophe's daughter] Glad you're here.
[kiss]
[exhales emotionally]
[sniffles]
[sighs]
[David] Hey.
That's your old man. Tough as nails. Hm?
You know he never quits.
[Christophe's daughter] I know.
So you know he's going to wake up.
Yeah. Yeah.
- [boyfriend] Do you want to get a coffee?
- Okay. sure.
The man who did this to him.
have you caught him yet?
We're on his trail.
It's just a matter of time.
[suspenseful music playing]
[officer 1 on radio]
Team 3 is being released.
[officer 2 on radio] Hold that position..
Team 5. you're on call at 300.
[man] Okay. guys. it's our shift.
Not much happening. is there?
[Chloé] There's no trace of CL-20
in the apartment
of our ex-soldier boy with the tattoos.
But last night he named the guy
who ordered the operation.
Francis Kröller.
A European arms dealer.
For a guy who sells guns.
that's sticking his neck out.
- Attacking a head of the task force?
- Yeah. it seems weird to me too.
We don't have his motive.
It might be personal or who knows.
We are sure that he organized the robbery.
And he's probably got the CL-20.
Section 3. you'll be on standby.
You'll handle the routine stuff.
Section 2. you're supposed to be off
but I want you on Kröller.
Intel's pursuing a lead
so let's be ready to move.
Excuse me.
I think Section 1 should be on Kröller.
But you've been on standby the whole week.
You just did an operation.
Yeah. that's true. General.
but we have experience with CL-20.
More importantly.
my team usually works with Tanya.
Come on. Kröller's a businessman.
not a field operative.
- He won't be wired up to a stack of CL-20.
- Excuse me. Chloé.
Your job is to get intel.
- Am I right?
- Yeah.
Yeah. so it would be a good plan
from now on for you to stay in your lane
and leave tactical decisions
to the tactical guys. okay?
Sure. You just want
to be the one to catch the guy.
I think you missed the point.
Sure. I answer to Éric and Arnaud.
but everyone here wants to catch him.
- Is that a problem? Should I apologize?
- And your team?
- Those guys need a break!
- Cool it!
- We're all on edge here.
- Sorry for caring about the teams!
Section 1 will be in charge of Kröller.
Okay? That's it.
You happy now?
Jerk.
[David] General! General!
I need to talk to you about Max.
Villiers. You know. Laurent's son?
- He just started.
- Yes. Sure.
I'm having a problem with the guy.
In terms of skills. uh. he's fine.
He knows his stuff. he performs.
I'm worried about his personality.
And his behavior.
[sighs] The kid is arrogant.
Full of himself.
He's got a real problem with authority.
- It's always got to be his way.
- Yeah. but you've all got that problem.
General.
He disobeyed a direct order
on his first mission.
So what do you recommend we do? Hm?
We made a mistake
when we admitted him to the unit.
I don't think he belongs in GIGN.
That's going pretty far
for the behavior you're describing.
My view is. don't do it.
But it's your section. Your decision.
Tomorrow we do the trust shooting.
I don't need to remind you.
The point of no return for new recruits.
If you're serious. do it now.
After that. he's one of us
whether you like it or not. okay?
- Fine.
- But. Commander.
Try to leave your emotions out of the job.
No. Wait a minute. General.
He may be Laurent's son and my godson.
but that's got--
No. no. I mean… I mean what happened
yesterday after the operation.
Okay.
Good.
[tense music playing]
[music fades]
Excuse me.
I'm looking for. uh. the auditorium.
- Do you know where it is?
- Uh. the big hall? It's down at the end.
- On the left.
- Thanks a lot.
[piano playing
"Impromptu No. 2" by Franz Schubert]
[note sustains]
No. no. no! Don't stop. don't stop.
Play the whole thing! Go on!
No. I can't do it.
[professor] Why can't you?
Ask yourself. why can't you do it?
- Because the piece is too fast for me.
- No. the piece isn't fast!
You can't do it because you haven't
practiced enough. Manon! That's all!
Okay. Let's break for lunch.
[chuckles]
[opens soda can]
So. what was the problem
you were having just now?
Didn't you practice enough.
or is the piece too difficult?
The problem is just that I'm not sure
if I should practice more or not at all.
What do you mean?
Nothing.
Come on. Tell me.
Why'd you come have lunch with me?
You've never done that before.
I came because I felt like seeing you.
That's all.
- That's all?
- Yeah. that's all.
- Okay.
- Okay. what?
- What's that supposed to mean?
- You won't want talk about it.
What? Sure I will.
Are you and Mom gonna split up?
Are you out of your mind?
Fine. Fine. you're not splitting up.
Where's all this coming from?
So you're going to Singapore too?
[poignant music playing]
Right. Mom's not all that good
at keeping secrets.
So what is it
you're trying to tell me here?
You'd rather live there with her?
That is so not what I'm talking about.
Singapore has one
of the best conservatories.
- Enough.
- Should I keep doing what I do?
- Never mind.
- Will I be able to make a living?
- Should I go in a different direction?
- You wanna go with her.
What I want most of all
is to talk to my dad.
He also took a test that was
extremely hard and he had to persevere.
I know what it's like
to doubt yourself every day.
I don't want him to think I'm choosing
Mom or that I'm forgetting about you.
I get it. I get it. I'm sorry.
Forgive me.
What does the piano mean to you?
[poignant music continues]
I…
Is it an instrument
that's just fun to you. or is it like.
when you wake up in the morning
and you go to bed at night.
the only thing you're thinking is.
play. play. play. play.
Play. play. play. play. play. play. play.
- Really?
- Yeah.
It's your passion?
Tsk. Yeah.
Okay. listen to what I'm about to say
because I'll only say it once.
Okay.
And I hope I don't live to regret it.
Don't let anything or anybody
get in the way of your dream.
Okay?
Because your passion
is what makes all the difference.
That means that when all the others
are frustrated or so tired they give up.
you'll still be sitting at the keyboard
just working.
And working. and working on your art.
That's what makes life worth living.
How you find your calling.
When you have that. it won't matter
what anybody else tells you.
You'll know who you are.
And it means that if the best school
really is in Singapore. well.
you have to go to Singapore.
[sighs]
Manon. don't let anyone
tell you otherwise.
- Not even your asshole of a father.
- [chuckles]
[drill whirring]
[Rapha continues drilling]
[hip-hop music plays in background]
Yeah. come on in.
Welcome.
- Pretty cool place. huh?
- Totally.
I'll give this a coat of paint. [chuckles]
And I'll patch all the holes there.
Do a bit of plastering.
And that wall needs some shelves.
- Where?
- There.
- It's a good idea. right?
- Yeah. it's cool.
Nice work you're doing.
Well. I figure I could easily be here
for 15 years. so why not fix it up?
[chuckles]
Come on. dude. What's with the mopey look?
Nothing.
I just don't feel all that welcome here.
Hey. It's done. We're here now. right?
Try to enjoy the moment.
I'll see you later. okay?
Okay.
- [Max] You know where David is?
- I saw him in the garage.
- [man whistling lilting melody]
- [somber music playing]
[car unlocks]
[Max] Hey!
Gonna see Christophe at the hospital.
You need something?
- I'll come with you.
- No. no. no. no.
I'm going alone.
You don't think I belong here?
You didn't even tell me
I did a good job yesterday.
Cédric. the others.
they all congratulated me.
Congrats.
Okay. I admit I went a bit far.
but we caught him. didn't we?
We caught him. Sure.
What's your problem?
Do you have a problem with me?
- Tell me!
- Tsk.
You know… [exhales]
After Dad died and you suddenly stopped
coming over to see me. I never blamed you.
I told myself. "He's busy."
"He's a hero like my dad. and…
one day I'll be with him on the force."
Then Mom told me
why you weren't around anymore.
It was too hard for you to see me.
I reminded you of him.
But it's not my fault that he died.
Doing this is my dream.
I busted my ass to be here.
Just as much as you do.
Tomorrow is the trust shooting.
I know I'll be there.
I hope you will too.
[dramatic music playing]
[dramatic music continues]
[music intensifies]
CREW
DIED IN THE LINE OF DUTY
FEBRUARY 10. 2010
[dramatic music continues]
[speaking indistinctly]
[music fades]
[exhales]
The trust shot
isn't the usual target practice.
It's a pact.
Between a mentor and a mentee.
[dramatic music playing]
Graduation was for your folks
and the academy.
The trust shot is for us.
And us only.
Your mentor will show you
that his faith in you is absolute.
And you'll prove that you've earned it.
[exhales]
This shot marks the true beginning
of your life in GIGN.
[exhales]
[applause]
[enthusiastic whistling]
[triumphant music playing]
[exhales]
[music fades]
[suspenseful music playing]
[exhales]
[triumphant music resumes]
[applause]
[whistling]
[cheering]
[phone beeping]
[Chloé] David!
- [cheering]
- [Chloé] David!
[whistles] David!
They located Kröller. Come on.
[Rapha] What's going on?
[music fades]
[man speaking in Spanish on TV]
[man continues speaking in Spanish on TV]
[dog snarls]
[whines]
- [man continues speaking in Spanish on TV]
- [dog whining]
[dog fusses]
[dog snarls]
[growls]
[whines]
[barks]
[birds chirping softly]
[sudden rumble]
[intense music playing]
[officers] Police!
Police! Police!
On the ground! Stop resisting!
- [woman] Let go!
- [officer 1] Stop resisting.
- [officer 2] On the ground! Now!
- [officer 3] To the rear!
- Let go!
- [officer 1] Stop moving!
[woman] Don't touch my children!
- Son of a bitch.
- [officer 1] Calm down.
- [woman] My children!
- Calm down!
- [officer 2] The kid has a gun.
- [officer 1] Easy. ma'am. Breathe.
- [Cédric] I got this.
- [woman] What are they doing to my son?
Julián!
[Cédric] Okay.
Give me what's in your hand.
- Okay?
- [officer 3] Clear!
[Cédric] Just give me what's in your hand.
- [breathing heavily]
- [tense music playing]
You're Julián.
Right?
My name's Cédric.
I work for the police. okay?
- Bullshit!
- Everything's fine.
- You can put that down now.
- You're gonna kill my father!
You came here to kill him!
[Cédric] We're not gonna kill anyone.
Everyone's fine.
Your family is safe and sound.
Give me what you're holding. Julián.
Give me what you've got there.
Damn it. kid. come on.
Drop the gun.
Come on. Julián.
Give me what's in your hand.
Your dad'll be fine.
[woman] Julián. do what he says.
Oh God. help me. What's happening?
Are you okay. sweetheart?
[Cédric] Easy now.
- [woman] What are you doing to my boy?
- [Cédric] That's it. Give it to me.
[tense music continues]
There we go.
That's it.
Gentle. now. It's all good.
[music fades]
Okay. up you get. Let's go find your mom
and your little brother. okay?
Come on. We'll both go.
[man 1 over radio] Command. Alpha One.
Primary objective secure.
[man 2] Copy. Alpha One. Hold positions.
Bravo team. status?
[man 3] Bravo here.
Med check complete. No injuries to report.
[man 2] Copy that. Bravo.
Evidence team is clear to enter.
[footsteps approaching]
Wait! We can make a deal. you and me.
[exhales]
I'm listening. Go on.
The guy who planted the bomb at the base.
I know who he is.
[ominous music playing]
Yeah. sure.
Here's where you tell me it wasn't you.
I'm a businessman. That's not my thing.
You made a quick buck on the CL-20.
You sold it. right?
No. no. That prick.
We made a deal.
He knew where to get the CL-20.
I supplied the men.
We'd split the explosives.
In the end. he kept it all for himself.
My crew double-crossed me. sided with him.
He screwed me. that bastard.
I get the picture.
He screwed you.
[music fades]
Who're we talking about?
Gimme the guy's name.
Tell me where I can find him.
Okay.
Let's make a deal. you and me. Right now.
You let all of us go.
and I tell you where to find him.
- [grunts]
- [Cédric] Hey!
David!
[grunts]
What the hell was that?
Come on. man. you're off the rails.
I'm not off the rails.
How about you take a break
and we'll handle this?
[indistinct radio chatter]
Djibril.
- You wanna take him?
- [Djibril] Yep.
Back seat of the Cayenne.
Thanks.
We'll escort him to the officer
who's controlling the perimeter.
You're with me. Max.
I don't have all day. Let's go.
Is he for real?
No. Other side. Max.
- You're driving.
- Okay.
[tense music playing]
Speed up. Max. This isn't a Sunday drive.
[engine revving]
- [gunshot]
- [David] Fuck!
[grunts]
Go. go. go!
[sniper rifle cocks]
[dramatic music playing]